bearville.com 2015-12-21

# Privacy Policy - Build-A-Bear Workshop US

*  About Us 
*  Guest Services 

  *  FAQs 
  *  Shipping Information 
  *  Build-A-Party 
  *  Return Policy 
  *  Privacy Policy 
  *  Supply Chain 
  *  Contact Us 

*  Our Products 

Build-A-Bear Workshop Privacy Policy - effective January 1st, 2014

**Scope:** This Privacy Statement applies to websites and retail stores operated by or on behalf of Build-A-Bear Workshop and its Affiliates worldwide.

Personal Information:

  * We collect the information you provide to us, such as your name, your postal address or email address, gender or date of birth. 
  * We collect non-personal information such as browser type and web pages visited to help manage our websites and to improve your overall experience. 
  * We use cookies and web beacons to manage our email programs and website. We do NOT use these technologies to collect or to store personal information. 
  * Click here for more information.

Uses:

  * We use the information you provide to register your friends in our ID tracking programs. 
  * We use the information you provide to create certificates for your new friends. 
  * We use the information you provide to place orders or book parties on our websites. 
  * If you tell us to, we will send you information about promotions and other marketing events via mail and email. 
  * We do NOT share your information with unrelated third parties for their marketing purposes. 
  * We use personal information consistent with the purpose you provided it to us. 
  * Click here for more information.

Important Information:

  * Build-A-Bear Workshop respects your privacy, and we will do our best to earn and keep your trust. 
  * Build-A-Bear Workshop complies with country data protection laws. 
  * Build-A-Bear Workshop complies with COPPA requirements. 
  * Click here for more information about COPPA.

* * *

How to Contact Us:

Write, call or email us at:

 **In the US and Canada:**  
Privacy Officer   
Build-A-Bear Workshop

1954 Innerbelt Business Center Drive  
St. Louis, MO 63114-5760

Email: [privacy@buildabear.com](mailto:privacy@buildabear.com?subject=US/CA%20privacy%20communication)  
Telephone: 1-877-789-BEAR (2327)

**In the United Kingdom:**  
Privacy Officer  
Build-A-Bear Workshop UK & Eire

St. Stephens House, Arthur Road  
Windsor, Berkshire SL4 RU

Email: [privacy@buildabear.co.uk](mailto:privacy@buildabear.co.uk?subject=UK%20privacy%20communication)  
Telephone: 0870 2245130
